{
    "subject": "resource/Matth\u00edas_Vilhj\u00e1lmsson",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Iceland",
    "human_readable": "Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson was born in Iceland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9711738228797913,
            "question": "Is Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson Icelandic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9513036608695984,
            "question": "Where was Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8245998620986938,
            "question": "What nationality is Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8070196509361267,
            "question": "What country is associated with Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7556182146072388,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7140308022499084,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Iceland besides its association with Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6697145700454712,
            "question": "Where might Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson have lived?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6601190567016602,
            "question": "Could Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson's birthplace have influenced his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5649644732475281,
            "question": "What is the significance of someone being born in Iceland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3013037145137787,
            "question": "Iceland is known for what?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson was born in Iceland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8198_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of someone being born in Iceland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8198_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson's birthplace have influenced his life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8198_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson have lived?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8198_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8198_44.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain:\n\nThe provided text states:  \"Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson was born on January 30, 1987, in \u00cdsafj\u00f6r\u00f0ur, Westfjords, Iceland.\" \n\nThis directly confirms that Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson was born in Iceland. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents contain information about Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson being an Icelandic footballer and being born in \u00cdsafj\u00f6r\u00f0ur, Westfjords, Iceland."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson, including that he is Icelandic and was born on January 30, 1987, in \u00cdsafj\u00f6r\u00f0ur, Westfjords, Iceland. This supports the statement that Matth\u00edas Vilhj\u00e1lmsson was born in Iceland."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}